<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learn the basics on</title><link>https://kubelt.com/docs/basics/</link><description>Recent content in Learn the basics on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kubelt.com/docs/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/introduction/</guid><description>What is Kubelt? # Kubelt&amp;rsquo;s integrated peer-to-peer edge architecture decentralizes any application. The Kubelt network is made of wallet-centric &amp;ldquo;Kubelt Cores&amp;rdquo; that look and behave any crypto wallets with the addition of content enabled APIs. These cores are configurable and composable in infinite ways with other peers on the network to create decentralized applications that fit your use case.
What content means to Kubelt really is anything! Kubelt Cores can host anything from web content, user databases, web assembly (compute), and more.</description></item><item><title>Why Kubelt?</title><link>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/why-kubelt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/why-kubelt/</guid><description>Stop paying the cloud tax! # Existing cloud providers surprise users with unfair fees that scale with the success of their applications.
With Kubelt, applications and content are optionally deployed to the edge over a decentralized, local-first content routing and delivery network called IPFS, saving users from egress and other variable cloud fees.
Users are the application # Traditional applications incentivize data aggregration that require large and expensive databases with complex governance overhead.</description></item><item><title>How it works</title><link>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/how-it-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/how-it-works/</guid><description>Kubelt Cores # At the heart of Kubelt is the &amp;ldquo;Kubelt Core&amp;rdquo;, an application container designed to look and feel just like a supercharged Web3 wallet.
The Kubelt Core extends the standard wallet APIs with multi-signer, content, and networking capabilities. These capabilities can be configured and organized in a way to build decentralized applications. Kubelt provides several libraries, tools and applications to work with and manage cores.
In essence, Kubelt Cores turns every user is a stand-alone, local-first, edge application that can be composed in a peer-to-peer configuration, unlocking endless possibilities.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/contributing/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Whitepaper</title><link>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/whitepaper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kubelt.com/docs/next/basics/whitepaper/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>